Switch on the power line
接上电源
Remember to put on
记得装备好你的
PROTECTION
护具绝缘
Lay down your pieces
摆好棋子
And let's begin
然后让我们开始
OBJECT CREATION
对象创建
Fill in my data parameters
输入我的数据参数
INITIALIZATION
数据初始化
Set up our new world
设定好我们的新世界
And let's begin the
然后让我们把
SIMULATION
模拟实现
world.execute(me);
歌曲：Mili
PV：땡닢（Eodslv）
If I'm a set of points
如果我是一组点
Then I will give you my
那么我将献给你
DIMENSION
我的次元
If I'm a circle
如果我是一个圆
Then I will give you my
那么我将献给你
CIRCUMFERENCE
我的圆圈
If I'm a sine wave
如果我是一条正弦波
Then you can sit on all my
那么请你坐上
TANGENTS
我的切线
If I approach infinity
如果我趋近于无穷
Then you can be my
那么你就是
LIMITATIONS
我的极限
Switch my current
切换我的电流
To AC to DC
从交流到直流
And then blind my vision
然后蒙上我的眼睛
So dizzy so dizzy
如此头晕目眩
Oh we can travel
我们可以穿越时空
To A.D to B.C
从西历到公元前
And we can unite
然后成为一体
So deeply so deeply
深入骨髓之间
If I can
如果我能
If I can give you all the
如果我能够献给你
STIMULATIONS
所有的刺激
Then I can
那么我就能够
Then I can be your only
那么我就能够成为你
SATISFACTION
唯一的满足
If I can make you happy
如果我能够让你开心
I will run the
那么我将
EXECUTION
执行指令
Though we are trapped
但我们被困
In this strange strange
在这个异乎寻常的
SIMULATION
模拟程序之间
If I'm an eggplant
如果我是一根茄子
Then I will give you my
那么我将献给你
NUTRIENTS
我的营养
If I'm a tomato
如果我是一颗番茄
Then I will give you
那么我将献给你
ANTIOXIDANTS
我的抗氧化物
If I'm a tabby cat
如果我是一只花猫
Then I will purr for your
那么我将咕噜咕噜
ENJOYMENT
只要你喜欢
If I'm the only god
如果我是唯一的神
Then you're the proof of my
那么你将是我
EXISTENCE
存在的证明
Switch my gender
切换我的性别
To F to M
从女到男
And then do whatever
只做想做的事
From AM to PM
从早到晚
Oh switch my role
切换我的角色
To S to M
从 S 到 M
So we can enter
这样我们就可以
The trance the trance
恍惚出神
If I can
如果我能
If I can feel your
如果我能够感受到
VIBRATIONS
你的振动
Then I can
那么我就能够
Then I can finally be
那么我就终于能够
COMPLETION
变得完全
Though you have left
但你还是走了
You have left
你走了
You have left me in
你把我抛弃
ISOLATION
在孤独之中
If I can
如果我能
If I can erase all the pointless
如果我能够消去这些无意义的
FRAGMENTS
碎片
Then maybe
那么可能
Then maybe you won't leave me so
那么我就可能不会
DISHEARTENED
如此失望
Challenging your god
与神作对
You have made some
你传给我的是
ILLEGAL ARGUMENTS
非法参数
EXECUTION
执行
死刑
EXECUTION
EIN
一
DOS
二
T  R  O  I  S
三
N  E
四
F    E    M
五
L    I    U
六
E   X   E   C   U   T   I   O   N
死   刑
If I can
如果我能
If I can give them all the
如果我能够给所有人
EXECUTION
赐予死刑
Then I can
那么我就能够
Then I can be your only
那么我就能够成为
EXECUTION
你唯一的命令
If I can have you back
如果你能够回到我身边
I will run the
那么我将
EXECUTION
执行指令
Though we are trapped
但我们已经被困
We are trapped
已经被困
I've studied
我学会了
I've studied how to properly
我学会了如何正确地去
LO-O-OVE
爱
Question me
提问我吧
Question me I can answer all
那些爱的问题
LO-O-OVE
我都能答对
I know the algebraic expression of
就连爱的代数表达式
LO-O-OVE
我也能够写出
Though you are free
虽然你已自由
I am trapped
我仍被困
Trapped in
LO-O-OVE
在爱之中
EXECUTION
死刑
字幕：t9tune
歌词翻译：髁恪(网易云音乐)
t9tune 部分修改
歌曲自 Project MILI
PV自 땡닢（Eodslv）
图片来自 The Noun Project
创作共用（CC）协议 署名 3.0 美国
分享、修改、署名，没有额外限制
（视频中使用的图标）
素材来自 Youtube
屏闪
来自 Footage Island (Nissim Farin)
花屏
来自 Creation Effects
感谢五个月来的等待。
感谢观看。
再见。